You sure can hold your drink, Chizuru.
Have some more.
Thank you.
What are you doing,
Ruka-chan?
We can't!
Seriously... We can't!
Bathroom break for me.
But Kazuya-san's in there.
Oh, right. I forgot.
Slide
Sorry.
I know I crossed a line there.
But I don't want to lose.
I have no regrets.
That stuff about your first kiss tasting
of lemons or strawberries was a lie, huh?
Mine just tasted a bit like booze.
Oh, Ruka-chan. Where's Kazuya-san?
He's using the bathroom.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Ring and Girlfriend"
Welcome back, Kazuya-san.
Took you long enough, Kazuya.
Y-Yeah?
Didn't you need the bathroom?
Oh, well, I don't need to anymore.
Are you two okay? You both look pale.
Yeah, where did all your energy go?
Did something happen?
N-Nah, we're totally... good!
Nothing about this is good!
An unmitigated disaster
What was that all about?
A kiss? Holy crap!
Ruka-chan and me?
Why'd we kiss? Why now?
You two are acting weird.
But I don't want to lose.
I was putting her through
more stress than I realized.
I mean, just thinking about it...
This whole fake relationship began because
Mizuhara and I didn't want to be exposed.
There were signs this was coming.
How she forced her way into my place,
her little "parting gift,"
and the way she snapped at Mami-chan...
I backed her into a corner!
And now...
Huh? Kiss?
Where did that come from?
Well, we've been dating for six months.
A normal couple would've kissed
by now, but I won't push my luck.
It's just...
I thought it would be such a happy moment
to share my first kiss with someone I love.
It was your first, Ruka-chan?
Are you sure you wanted it to be with me?
Hell no, that's obviously not right!
Wasting your first kiss on this
pathetic excuse for a relationship...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Ruka-chan!
This is on me! It's all my fault!
Oh, I nearly forgot.
I have a gift for you, Chizuru-san.
That box...!
It's the ring my husband
gave me when he proposed.
The engagement ring?
The implications..!!
It went to Harumi-san later,
but we were talking, and we wanted to give
it to you to celebrate your 20th birthday.
Right, Harumi-san?
Yes, please have it.
Yeah, no! On a scale of nope to nope, nope!
She can't accept that!
Who would give an engagement ring
to a girlfriend who just turned 20?!
Who gives a family heirloom
to a rental girlfriend?!
I hope it suits you!
You're getting
carried away, Gran.
What kind of insane
situation is this?
We have nothing else to offer you,
It may be old,
but it's quality.
and this bag of bones couldn't think of an
appropriate gift for an angel like you...
Oh, no...
Tee
hee.
Wait!
I can't take something so important to you!
It's fine. We want you to have it.
B-But...
Mizuhara can't deal with this.
And of course she can't!
She's probably never faced a
situation like this before!
I gotta figure something out, and fast!
What's with the hand?
What does this mean? What are you
trying to tell me, Ruka-chan?
Duh! This has gotta be hard
for her to watch, too.
What do I do? What can I do?
I'm thinking of quitting
the rental girlfriend job.
I figure it's about time to move on.
Would you please try it on?
I really can't...
We can't accept it.
Well, I do understand,
but there's no need to overthink it.
It's not about that.
I can't have Chizuru accepting that ring!
This is it.
What do you mean, Kazuya?
There's no other way.
I'm sorry about this.
I know you love Chizuru.
I know you'll hate me for doing
this during the birthday party.
Gran's gonna bawl her eyes out!
I don't wanna see it!
Or maybe she'll disown me?
Either way, it's gonna suck.
But there's no avoiding it anymore.
I know I'm going to put a damper on
things, but this can't keep going.
Mizuhara and I going on dates
is stressing Ruka-chan out.
I have to do this for her, too.
Besides, I need to end this...
sooner rather than later.
Then do it right here, and now, tonight!
I just can't let things stand.
Thanks for everything, Mizuhara.
Stay calm and hear me out.
Chizuru and I...
Forgive me, Ruka-chan!
I can't continue with this farce
if it's gonna keep hurting people!
We... We broke...
S-Sorry!
Third Hospital
Itabashi, Tokyo
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello? This is Ichinose.
What? Really?!
I'll be right there!
Please handle things!
That was the moment everything began.
My grandma lost consciousness...
Rent-a-Girlfriend
We're BFFs.
Itabashi Third Hospital
I'll handle the fare. You two go on ahead.
But the money...
Let's go.
Please be there for Chizuru.
Granny Sayuri!
Oh, Kazuya-kun! And Chizuru, too.
Sweat        Sweat
Chizuru-peeled
That's my Sayutaso!
You came back from a trip to the afterlife?
I admire your will to live!
Indeed, I made an about turn
when I got to the River Styx.
You gave the devil himself
an attitude adjustment, huh?
Can these two be any more inappropriate?!
I'm so sorry I ruined your
birthday party, though.
My body can't
take a hint.
Oh, please.
I'm
really
sorry.
I should be the one apologizing for inviting
Chizuru when you were under the weather.
I feel bad.
You have nothing to feel bad about.
Given how much Chizuru looked
like she wanted to go,
I would've made her skip
my own funeral for it.
Huh? Mizuhara did?
ba-dump
C-Come on, Grandma! What are you saying?
Oh, is that so, Chizuru-san?
She wanted to come over to my place?
Well, yes...
glance
glare...
Got carried away.
S-Sorry.
Room 301
Ichinose Sayuri
nyuk    nyuk
hehe
nod
We panicked for a while there,
ahaha
hyuk      hyuk
hehe
nyuk    nyuk
nod
but I'm glad Granny Sayuri's all right.
ahaha
hyuk      hyuk
nyuk    nyuk
hehe
nod
ahaha
hyuk      hyuk
I guess Mizuhara must be relieved, too.
Grandma, you need to get some rest.
Come in.
Ichinose-san, can we talk?
Sure. Please watch over them, Kazuya-san.
S-Sure.
That was so naturally couple-like.
Smirk
Say, how is it going with Chizuru?
What do you mean, how?
They're too bashful to tell me.
Are you all lovey-dovey?
I-I guess?
We talked about them
moving in together today.
What? Moving in?!
Wouldn't that be nice?
Be still, my beating heart!
I'm glad she was all right,
but I lost my chance to spill the beans.
There's the whole thing with Ruka-chan, too.
I can't just let things be.
H-Hey, Mizuhara.
They sent me on an errand,
those slave drivers.
What did the doctor say?
Bad news.
My grandmother's not doing too great.
The doctor said so.
Watch. This is my new favorite
streamer. Seventy years old.
She seems perfectly fine,
Wow, that's pretty close to us.
but she doesn't have much time left.
Is it gonna be okay?
Like I just said, definitely not okay.
No, are you okay?
What, you're worried about me now?
Yes, I'm okay.
I knew this was coming
ever since I heard her diagnosis,
so I did everything I could do for her.
Wait, where are you going?
Isn't that obvious?
I'm gonna tell your grandma that
our relationship was a lie.
What? But...
I started it, and I'm gonna see it through.
I can't cause you any more trouble.
I won't talk about the rental thing,
but if we're running out of time,
all the more reason to come clean.
This is all I can do to make things right.
Wait. Hold on.
I don't want her to know.
I don't want to tell Grandma
that we're breaking up.
Mizuhara?
You don't want to tell her? But why?
Because she's taken a real liking to you.
And she's worried that I'll end
up all alone after she's gone.
I know I'm contradicting myself after
telling you to make things right.
But there's really no point now.
Telling a woman on her deathbed that her
granddaughter just broke up with her boyfriend
isn't going to help in any way.
B-But...
We're not actually going out, are we?
No.
We're not.
Th-Then how is continuing to lie gonna help?
It's become more than just a lie.
I don't have it in me to
make her sad at this point.
B-But...
Why do it?
As far as my grandma knows,
I've found myself a wonderful guy.
Why break that spell?
I'm heading back.
What the hell am I supposed to do?
I get what Mizuhara's saying,
but is this really okay?
Is it really the right thing to do?
I mean, it's not like I want to
make Granny Sayuri sad, either.
Droop
Scratch
My back's
against the wall!!
This "I nearly had a heart attack!"
caption is a running gag. I love it.
yay    yay
nyuk nyuk
That looks like fun.
Maybe I should try it out, too.
Okay, we're going to head out.
Visiting hours are long over.
Sure. Do visit again, Nagomin.
You betcha.
I'll go hail a cab.
Itabashi Third Hospital
Okay. Make sure it's a pretty one.
Those don't exist.
One like a pumpkin carriage, for my angel.
Chizuru-san.
About this ring...
Sorry, I can't accept it.
Sayuri-san's not going to make it, is she?
Such a strong woman.
She's acting all cheery,
but one look at her face
tells the whole story.
I heard that you'd have no family
left if worse comes to worse.
If you ever need money, pawn it off.
And no need to wear it if you don't want to.
I just want you to have it.
That's really it.
Hey, our ride's here!
Good. Why is hailing cabs the
only thing you're so good at?
Is it because
you're big?
Mizuhara was putting on a brave face...
What's your address, Chizuru-san?
Oh, she'll be staying with me tonight.
Our addresses
are the same!
...but she looked smaller to me that day.
Ah, yes, a great idea.
She was probably weighed down
by pain, fear, sorrow,
and lots of other emotions.
B-Bye.
Yeah.
And yet here I am,
unable to do anything for her.
Wow, look who
decided to show up.
You better have bought
some good feed!
Isn't that good enough?
Damn it.
Ugh...
Rainbow (made of candy)
Angel Wings
Cream Clouds
Super
delish!!!
This cream just melts in your mouth!
om nom
clatter
The rainbow's great, too!
What is even going on here?
fluff
This is no time to be eating fluffy pancakes.
Nice and sweet...
I went and dug in...
Is she not finding this awkward?
It's so unbearable for me
that I can't even look her in the eye.
om      nom
Is she okay?
Chizuru-san's grandmother, I mean.
Oh, yeah, her condition
stabilized last night.
Really?
Sorry we made you go home alone.
Don't worry about it. It was an emergency.
There's no point in making her worry.
And Chizuru-san?
Was she having a hard time?
Yeah. She was trying not
to show it, but I bet.
Oh... I guess it would be hard on her.
Ruka-chan's such a nice girl.
Even now, she's worrying about Mizuhara.
I'm not sure I'd be able to.
I'm calling a truce with you and Chizuru-san.
Sure, I do want to be your girlfriend for real,
but even I know this isn't the
time to go on the offensive.
Ruka-chan...
It made me happy
to see you try to draw a
line in the sand with her.
But now's a terrible time.
What? She figured it out?!
It was obvious, huh?
Also, you have the wrong
idea about something.
I did say I don't want to lose,
but I also said I had no regrets.
It did get me down seeing
how perfect Chizuru-san was,
but it only made me realize once again
how much I loved you... hence the kiss.
I got to kiss the person I love and
push our relationship one step forward,
so I've made some real progress!
Ruka-chan...
Thank you!
By the way, whenever you wanna
do it, just let me know.
Kissing is fair game now, right?
No, it's not! Not even close!
What?
Such a shy boy.
Oh, right, here's your birthday present.
gloom
What is even going on?
I finally made up my mind,
but now Mizuhara and
Ruka-chan are against it?
I'm calling a truce.
They're both so much more mature than me.
Gah! You've gotta be kidding me!
There's not a damn thing left for me to do!
Woof!!
Ichinose
I'm done...
It's all over.
What the hell am I supposed to do?!
Somebody help me!!
With all my heart and soul
Kazuya-kun's Birthday
Let's do this!
I've turned over a new leaf.
Let's call a truce for the
time being, Chizuru-san.
But promise me one thing.
No kissing Kazuya-kun, okay?
Relax. I won't do anything.
Wha?!
Uh...?
Oh, nothing!
Right. He's the one to keep an eye on!
Call off the truce!
What happened to turning over a new leaf?!
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Guide and...
...Girlfriend."
If I need to, I'll chain him up...
"Guide and Girlfriend"
Ruka-chan?!